Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Warner-Lambert, 1961-1996, 20 boxes
  - Audiovisual Materials
    - Originals (CLOSED: Need use copies)
      - Videocassette
        - OR30: Portugal: Trident Desert Expedition Tape 2. Undated. Format: U-matic. (Box WL22)
        - OR31: Puerto Rico: MFP&W (Listerine, Lubriderm, Chiclets). 1996. Format: Beta (NTSC). (Box WL22)
        - OR32: South Africa (Cape Town): Vita C, Schick, Clorets, Hall, Chiclets. Undated. Format: VHS. (Box WL23)
        - OR33: Spain: Warner-Lambert 35th Anniversary. 1996. Format: Beta. (Box WL23)
        - OR34: Switzerland: Trident Kaugummi 1979/80. 1996. Format: Beta. (Box WL23)
        - OR35: Taiwan: Interview with client for ARB. Undated. Format: VHS. (Box WL23)
        - OR36: Taiwan: Listerine, Clorets showreel. 1996. Format: Beta SP. (Box WL23)
        - OR37: United Kingdom (Manchester): Clorets compilation. 1996. Format: VHS (NTSC). (Box WL23)
        - OR38: Venezuela: Warner-Lambert commercials. 1996. Format: U-matic. (Box WL23)
  - Oversized Materials
    - General--Articles, 1956-1983 (Box WL-OV1)
    - Products--Chewels
      - Research, 1984 (Box WL-OV1)
      - Storyboards, 1981-1983 (Box WL-OV1)
    - Products--Chewing gum, American Chicle regional distribution map, 1983 (Box WL-OV1)
    - Products--E.P.T., advertising designs, 1979-1981 (Box WL-OV1)
    - Products--Listerine
      - Advertising designs, 1983-1991 (Box WL-OV1)
      - Labels, undated (Box WL-OV1)
      - Storyboards, 1989-1991 (Box WL-OV1)
    - Products--Sticklets, storyboards, 1983 (Box WL-OV1)
    - International--Hungary, Halls advertisements, 1995 (Box WL-OV1)
    - Scrapbook, 1922-1927 (Box WL-OV2)
    - General--Nielson Station Index Map, 1983 (Oversize-folder WL-OF1)